接着转  接着转
And turn. And turn.
- 接着转  接着转  - 停
- And turn. And turn. - And stop.
丽芙  我又不是你的御用超模
Liv, I'm not your personal supermodel.
哦  玛蒂  我从来没说过你是啊
Oh, Maddie, I never said you were.
你可是我的三维镜子
You are my 3-d mirror.
那好
Okay.
你的三维镜子就要辞职不干了
Well, your 3D mirror is about to quit.
我这周要和灰熊队打一场比赛
I have a big game against the grizzlies this week
这双脚将是要上篮球场的
and these feet need to be on a basketball court.
- 所以  - 啊  我可要提醒你
- So... - Ah! Need I remind you
这次时尚的小短会算是次报复
that this little fashion sesh is payback
报复你把我最喜欢的羊绒衫混在别的衣服里面  洗的缩水缩成这样
for you tossing my favorite cashmere sweater in the laundry.
好吧
Okay.
为什么女孩子都这么痴迷于鞋子啊
Why do girls get so excited about shoes?
我的意思是  它们不过就是用来垫脚的嘛
I mean, they're just things to put on your feet
这样你踩到一坨大粪就不会得钩虫病了
so that if you step in dog poop you don't get hookworm.
玛蒂  一双合适的高跟鞋能让一个女孩感到魔力四射
Maddie, the right pair of heels can make a girl feel magical.
而她的妈妈也可以借走享受享受魔力
And her mother when she borrows them.
站住
Stop.
你们为什么要拖着一堆树枝穿堂入室啊
Why are you dragging tree branches through the house?
如果穿过房子而不是绕过房子的话
Going through the house instead of around
能让我们提前 27 步抵达削木机
gets us to the wood chipper 27 steps faster.
顺便还能让我们在厨房喝一杯又冰又甜的柠檬水
Plus we can stop in the kitchen for a nice, cold glass of lemonade.
对哦  不过这还会在房子里留下一堆等着某人收拾的烂叶子
Right. It also creates a trail of leaves for someone to clean up later.
噢
Oh.
好了  把东西收拾好吧
Okay, well, let's... let's wrap this up.
别这样  玛蒂  难道这里就没有一点点合你口味的东西么
Come on, Maddie, there's not even a little part of you that's enjoying this?
等一下  丽芙  让我想一想
Oh, hold on, Liv. Let me check real quick.
呃  一点都没有
Um... no.
真的吗
Seriously?
得了吧  玛蒂  你不能整辈子都只穿运动鞋啊
Okay, you can't wear sneakers for the rest of your life, Maddie.
你猜怎么着  你要激发你内心的光芒
You know what... you need to tap into your inner sparkle.
让你的小四眼好好欣赏欣赏  这双鞋
Feast your four eyes... on these!
我已经找到了最好的高跟鞋
I have found the perfect pumps.
哦  闻起来就像走在时尚最前沿的一碗布丁上一样
Oh! It's as if you were walking around in a bowl of high-fashion pudding.
好的  好的  你够了
Okay, okay, enough.
我会试穿它的
I will try them on.
好吧  但是要小心  你一旦把它撑大了我就穿不了了
Okay, just be careful, 'cause if you stretch 'em I can't wear 'em.
你们有十秒的时间
You guys have ten seconds.
抓紧看吧
Look quick.
10  9  8
10, 9, 8...
哇  我的亲娘啊
Whoa, mama.
原来这就是由内而外的光芒啊
Hello, inner sparkle.
我爱死这双鞋了
I love these shoes.
我真讨厌这双鞋
I hate these shoes.
好吧  你能骗一个假小子穿上女装  但你永远没法让她美丽动人的
Well, you can lead a tomboy to designer shoes but you can't make her shimmer.
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
b... b... better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
-  I'm up with the sunshine -  Let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
-  I lace up my high tops -  Oh no
扣篮  热热身
-  slam dunk -  Ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
-  I'm under the spotlight -  Holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go, go, go
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the other half of me, me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the better half of me, me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
来尝尝  鲁尼女士
Here you go, Mrs. Rooney.
我烤制了新鲜的松饼
I baked fresh muffins.
我的哥们埃文真是个好客人
My buddy Evan is the perfect houseguest.
他自己整理床铺  他帮着拿报纸
He makes his bed. He gets the paper.
他还会烤松饼
He bakes fresh muffins.
简直是太周到了
He's just so thoughtful,
而且干活的时候满是雀斑的小脸上堆满了笑容
and does it all with a smile on that sweet, freckly face.
他让我看起来糟透了
He's really making me look bad.
好的  谢谢你  埃文
Well, thank you, Evan.
我还没习惯这么贴心的照顾
I am not used to all this attention.
咳咳
Ahem.
长命百岁
Bless you?
我太谢谢你们能在我妈出去开会的时候让我住在这儿了
I really appreciate you letting me stay here while my mom's at a convention.
为什么不休息一下  等我把这里收拾干净呢
Why don't you take a few minutes for yourself and I'll clean up here?
你简直是个小天使啊
You are like a dream.
帕克  你也该从你朋友那里学到些什么了吧
Parker, you could learn a little something from your friend.
伙计  我们要谈谈
Dude, we gotta talk.
太棒了  我妈说谈话是给精神减负的最好方法
Great! My mom says talking is the best way to unburden your soul.
我理解你想多帮帮忙的心情  但是你给我妈做的事越多
I totally get you're trying to be helpful, but the more you do for my mom,
她对我的期望值就越大
the more she'll expect from me.
我现在生活过得这么舒坦
I got a good thing going here.
我绝不需要你插一脚来毁掉了它
And I don't need you waltzing in and ruining it!
我妈说帮人做事就像是释放光芒
My mom says being helpful is a ray of light
我可以以此照亮温馨的小家
I can just shine on our happy home.
那是假话
Not true.
她这么说是想在家务活上偷懒呢
The goal is to get out of chores.
噗
Pfft.
帕克  你真逗啊
Parker, you're hilarious.
哦  等等  你是认真的么
Oh, wait, you're serious?
如果你的父母认为你干什么事都干不成
If your parents think that you're not capable of doing anything,
你就不需要做任何家务活了
you'll never have to do another chore again.
那个世界难道存在么
Does such a world exist?!
确实存在
It does.
让我来教你一套方法
Let me show you a way.
更好的方法
A better way.
帕克的方法
The Parker way.
C+
C-plus?
还是体育
In gym?
爸
Dad.
哈  亲爱的戴个哨子的父亲大人
Ha! Loving father man who wears the whistle.
如果你不能让我的平均分变得好看些  我就永远都致不了毕业辞了
If I don't keep my perfect G.P.A., I will never be valedictorian.
而且我在机器人社里牛皮吹得老大
And I have been talking a lot of smack in robotics club.
所以还造了个会吹牛大吹特吹的机器人
So has the smack-talking robot I built.
抱歉了  儿子  但是我必须要给你打低分
Sorry, son, but I had to mark you down
因为你没能在 35 秒内完成折返跑
because you didn't finish your shuttle run in under 35 seconds.
35 秒  爸爸  那是不可能的
35 seconds? Daddy, that's impossible.
噢  是吗
Oh, yeah?
嘿  迪吉
Hey, Diggie.
你跑一趟折返跑看看
We're go for shuttle run.
现在开始计时
Timer starts now.
如果你想要的话  可以让你重考
If you want, I can give you a retest,
但你只能有一次机会
but you're only going to get one shot at it.
你的意思是我唯一能保证毕业的方法
You're telling me the only way I'm going to be valedictorian
就是像只蟑螂一样发疯的在体育馆里来回跑
is if I scurry across the gym floor like a jock-roach.
我又不是定规则的人  孩子
I don't make the rules, son.
我只是负责吹哨的
I just blow the whistle.
同时  我还教你们生理课
Also, I teach health class.
所以一旦你们对自己青春期的变化有什么疑问
So if you have any questions about your changing body,
我的门随时为你们敞开
my door is always open.
算了吧  还是把门关了得了
Yeah, let's keep that door closed.
完成了
Done!
折返跑跑得不错啊  迪吉
Nice shuttle run, Diggie.
28.7 秒
28.7 seconds.
我认为这是最好成绩了  孩子
I don't think any less of you, son.
嘿
Hey!
迪吉
Diggie.
我最爱的校队运动员
My favorite varsity athlete
也是唯一一个从不打击贬低我的家伙
and the only one who has never purpled my nurples.
我需要你帮个忙
I need a favor.
我必须在 35 秒内跑完折返跑
I need to do the shuttle run in under 35 seconds.
哦  你想让我来训练你
Oh, so you want me to train you?
- 我很乐意  - 其实  我想让你当枪手来替我跑
- I'd be happy to. - Actually, I was thinking you'd do it for me.
我给你戴副眼镜
I'd give you some glasses.
穿上古怪的筒形袜
Some fancy tube socks.
乔伊  无意冒犯  但是没人会认为我就是你的
Joey, no offense, but no one's going to believe that I'm you.
你猜怎么着  你说的很对
You know what... you're right.
为何我天生就这么帅气啊
Why did I have to be born so handsome?
噢  嘿
Oh, hey.
听说你感觉不太舒服
Heard you weren't feeling very well.
啊  是的  大概是蠕虫病什么的吧
Oh, yeah. Must be a bug or something.
唔  我希望你明天对阵灰熊队的比赛能发挥正常啊
Mm, well, I hope you'll be okay for the game against the grizzlies tomorrow.
我觉得经过一晚上的睡眠应该能恢复好的
I'm pretty sure I'll be fine after a good night's sleep.
嗯哼  要我给你拿点姜汁汽水么
Mm-hmm. Can I get you some ginger ale?
或是一些咸饼干
Or some crackers?
呃  不用了  我感觉挺好的
Um, no, I'm... I'm fine.
而且我的床在这边
I'm also over here.
你在找什么呢
What are you looking for?
哦
Oh!
有点头脑发热吧
A fever.
哎呀呀
Aww!
嘿  妈  妈
Hey, mom. Mom.
咋了
Hmm?
你在找丽芙的那双漂亮鞋子  对不
You're looking for Liv's perfect pumps, aren't you?
什么  才不是呢
What? No.
不  我  我根本停不住对鞋的思念
No, I... I can't stop thinking about them.
我想立马穿上
I want to slip 'em on.
哪怕只穿一个趾头  我就是想过过瘾
Even just a toe. I just need a taste.
呃  那个  其实高跟鞋不在这里
Mm, yeah, well, they're actually not in here.
我刚看见丽芙来过找了一轮了
I just saw Liv coming and looking for them.
所以我要是看见了的话会通知你的
So if I see them, I will let you know.
但是  嘿  妈妈  与此同时
But... hey, mom. In the meantime,
你或许应该想想你的尊严该穿在哪里
you might want to slip on a size 10 dose of dignity.
你说得对
You're right.
我不知道我怎么像着了魔一样
I don't know what's gotten into me.
如果你胆敢告诉丽芙我来过这儿  你就会
If you tell Liv I was here, and you will be...
我到底是怎么了
what's wrong with me?
嗨  宝贝们
Hi, girls.
我刚骗走了我妈
I just lied to my mom.
还是关于鞋子的
About shoes.
哈  而且我根本就不在乎
Ha! And I don't even care.
这就是我的储物柜啦
And this is my locker.
宝贝们  快躲好
Hide, girls.
噢  你好啊  玛蒂
Oh, hi, Maddie.
我很高兴看见你的感觉好多了
I'm glad you're feeling better.
什么  哦  对
What? Oh. Yeah.
好一大截了
Way better.
呃  那个  刚刚我听见两个学生
Um... Oh, wow. You know what... I hear two students
在拐角那儿试着处理一些情感问题呢
trying to work through an emotional issue around the corner.
我来了  让路
I'm coming. Make way.
心理治疗师驾到了
Therapist coming through!
鲁尼
Rooney.
你昨天怎么了
What happened to you yesterday?
我们本来约好一起吃冰淇淋的哟
We were supposed to meet for fro-yo.
但你没出现哟
You didn't show-yo.
俺就只能打包先走了哟
Had to get it to go-yo.
呃  对  你收到我的短信了吗
Uh, yeah. Didn't you get my text?
呃  收是收到了  但是“来不了  有事”
Well, yeah, but... "can't come. Got a thing."
讲得不明不白的
Is not all that informative.
你是不是长高了
Did you get taller?
不  是  也许吧
No. Yes. Maybe.
也许是你变高了
Maybe you're taller.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
玛蒂  你看起来不一样了
Maddie, you look different.
也许是你变高了
Maybe you're taller!
好吧
Okay...
等等  刚才那下不对劲  对不
Okay, that was weird, right?
我知道不对劲长什么样  刚才那就是了
I know weird, and that was it.
但她一整天都这么不对劲
But she's been acting weird all day.
她居然今天都没有晨练
She even skipped her morning workout.
这真不是她的风格
That's so not like her.
等等  你怎么知道  她都是早上 5 点就起来晨练的
Wait, how would you know? She works out at 5:00 A.M.
- 我一直在为你教我的折返跑复试而锻炼  - 真的吗
- I was up doing the drills you taught me for my shuttle run retest. - Really?
不  我当时在熬夜看神龙小说
Nope. I was up reading a book about dragons.
- 嘿  乔伊  - 维罗
- Hey, Joey. - Willow!
哇  我以前还从没见过他跑
Wow. I've never seen him run before.
真奇怪  我见到他他都是撒丫子跑的
That's weird. I only see him run.
好的  等我妈进来  我们该做什么呢
Okay, when my mom comes in, what are we going to do?
降低她的期望值
Lower her expectations.
正是
Exactly.
准备好体验一下帕克的方法发威吧
Get ready to experience the Parker way in action.
- 你好啊  鲁尼女士  - 哦
- Hey, Mrs. Rooney. - Oh.
你知道你现在有很多活要干
I know you have a lot to do around here.
我帮你把洗碗机里的碟子都拿出来了
So I unloaded the dishwasher for you.
谢谢你了  埃文
Well, thank you, Evan.
哦  那些碟子还都是脏的呢
Oh, but those dishes were dirty.
只不过有一点脏罢了
They seemed a little crusty.
不过我才不介意您怎么操持家务呢
But I'm not here to judge how you keep house, ma'am.
抱歉了  鲁尼女士
Sorry, Mrs. Rooney.
让我来帮您吧
Let me help you.
抱歉
Oops.
拜托  埃文
Come on, Evan.
以后做事请小心一点啊
Be a little more careful.
哎呀
Oops.
看来我被埃文带的也笨手笨脚的了
Looks like I caught the clumsies from Evan.
孩子们  停手吧
Boys, please stop.
我很抱歉  鲁尼女士
I feel terrible, Mrs. Rooney.
我去拿把拖把把这里收拾了吧
Let me get the broom and help clean up.
别别别  别帮我
No no no. Do not help.
这事还是我自己来比较好
I will take care of this myself.
谁的方法
What's the way?
帕克的方法
The Parker way.
有谁看见玛蒂了么
Has anybody seen Maddie?
比赛还有两分钟就开始了
Our game starts in two minutes.
玛蒂还没有来
Maddie's not here?
她可从来没有缺席过一场比赛的啊
She's never missed a game.
等等  要是玛蒂没有来  我就得上场了啊
Wait, if Maddie doesn't show, that means I have to play.
这可不能这样啊  天
That can't happen, man.
我本来还打算在比赛的时候把作业写了呢
During the game is when I get my homework done.
玛蒂今天表现的很是奇怪啊
Maddie was acting really weird today.
她是不是长高了
And did she get taller?
长高了
Taller?
大概长高了多少  是不是 7 公分左右
Like how much taller? Like 2 1/2 inches taller?
差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
她看上去变了个人似的
She just seemed different.
她居然在那咯咯笑  玛蒂才不会这么笑
She giggled. Maddie doesn't giggle.
她一直都是哼哼的
She snorts.
她今天整个感觉都像是由内而外透出某种光芒似的
It's like she had some kind of inner sparkle, man.
鞋子
The shoes.
我想我应该知道她在哪里了
Um, I think I know where she might be.
我这就去叫她
So I will just go get her.
嗯
Yeah.
你看看能不能把表演拖一会
See if you can get them to hold curtain.
天  这姑娘真心不了解运动啊
Wow, that girl really doesn't get sports.
好吧  小污点  该你上场了
All right, stains. You're in.
好吧
Fine.
我又不知道今天要我上场
I didn't think I was going to play today.
玛蒂
Maddie.
嘿  丽芙
Hey, Liv.
你来有何贵干
What are you doing here?
我来接你去参加那场比赛
Well, I'm here to take you back to the game.
不过这是怎么回事
But what is all of this?
哦  你可是说对了
Oh, you were so right.
我可喜欢这双鞋子了
I love these shoes!
哦
Oh!
这事情我们可以稍后再谈
Well, okay, we can talk about that later.
你先把这双鞋子脱了  我这就要接你去参加比赛
Just kick those off and we will get you back to the game.
噗  我才不去什么比赛咧
Pfft. I'm not going back to that game.
你到底是谁
Who are you?
我是一个喜欢穿高跟鞋  闪闪发亮的软妹子
I am a shoe-loving sparkly girl.
你要不要和我一起模仿那些超模啊
Do you want to play supermodel with me?
呵呵
Yeah.
当然了
Of course I do.
停  停  停  停
No no no no.
这  这腔调不对
This... this is wrong.
玛蒂整个失控了
Maddie was out of control.
呼  这个任务看来比我想象的困难多了
Whew, this was a much bigger job than I thought it was going to be.
我肯定是要找后援了
And I was definitely going to need backup.
不过
But first...
行  就一分钟
Okay, one minute.
好的
Yes.
您真的不需要我们帮什么忙么  妈
Are you sure we can't help you with something, mom?
哦  不  你们两个小家伙就在这里给我好好坐着
Oh, no. You boys just sit here and do not lift a finger.
免得又磕了碰了  把什么东西打了
You might break one of them too.
我得去处理一下后院里面那堆事情
I am going to do some yard work.
遵命
You're the boss.
任务达成
Mission accomplished.
帕克的方法
The Parker way.
这机器真赞
It's beautiful.
您在干什么呢  鲁尼女士
Um, what are you doing, Mrs. Rooney?
哦  你懂的  把这些残枝断梗的
Oh, you know, just jamming these big branches
塞进这台有 40 片旋转不锈钢刀片的
into this hundred-horsepower monster
上百马力的机器里面
with 40 razor-sharp stainless steel teeth.
哇
Whoa!
不会吧  我们能帮忙么
No way. Can we help?
呵呵  孩子  要是我不觉得你能把盘子放到水盆里面而不打掉
Oh, sweetie, if I can't trust you to carry your plate to the sink,
我怎么可能让你靠近这台机器呢
then I sure can't trust you around this bad boy.
此话当真
Seriously?
我没有比这更想做的事情了啊
But there is nothing I've ever wanted to do more.
话说  既然我这么想了  我要取消你的空手道课
You know, now that I think about it, I'm pulling you out of karate
我也要在你的自行车上重新装上从轮
and I'm putting the training wheels back on your bike.
好消息是  我帮你们买了蜡笔和安全剪刀
But the good news is... bought you some crayons and safety scissors.
就在里面  要我抱你进去么
They're inside. You want uppy?
做的不错啊  帕克
Nice work, Parker.
我们就连这个都做不成了
We got ourselves out of that one.
赞啊
Sweet!
这是那款 64 色的
It's the 64 pack.
盒子里面还有内置的卷笔刀呢
It has a sharpener built into the box.
哦  等等  你妈妈把那个也拿走了
Oh, wait. Your mom took that out.
耶  宝贝
Yeah, baby!
天  这听上去还真有趣
Man, that sounds like fun.
比这还有趣
More fun than all this?
这套里面有深棕黄色的蜡笔呢
Burnt sienna.
喔呼
Whoo-hoo!
我不敢相信她居然不让我们两个帮忙
I can't believe she's not letting us help.
正是
Exactly.
拜你所赐  她以后再也不会让我们做这种有趣的事情了
Thanks to you, she'll never let us do stuff like that again.
我们要不要击掌
Can a brother get a fist bump?
是不是说我如果什么都不做  就什么都做不成了
So if I don't ever do anything, I don't ever get to do anything?
这是我对帕克的方法的基本理解
It was my understanding that was the primary message of the Parker way.
看来帕克的方法误入歧途了
Well, perhaps the Parker way is misguided.
新鲜的松饼能不能让你觉得好过一点
Would fresh-baked muffins make this better?
当然
Certainly couldn't hurt.
好吧  乔伊  你能办到的
All right, Joey. You got this.
在这个弱不禁风的身体里面
Inside this scrawny, un-athletic, muscle-free sack of bones
是一个往返跑高手
is a natural-born shuttle runner.
您这么对我说我很荣幸
That means a lot coming from you.
但是丝毫无用啊
But it's useless.
我不可能在 35 秒里面跑完往返跑
There is no way I can do this in 35 seconds.
我的毕业致辞就算是泡汤了
I can kiss valedictorian a good-bye.
老兄  你能行的
Dude, it's going to be okay.
你只要充分信任你的第一感觉
Just trust your instincts.
这个叫迪吉的兄弟多少还是有些锦囊妙计的
And know that the dig-man still has a couple tricks up his sleeve.
还有  你最好把鞋带系好
Also, you might want to tie your shoe.
啊  呵呵  是啊
Ah, pfft. Yeah.
准备好了么  乔伊
All right, Joey.
这是你往返跑补考的唯一一次机会
You get one last shot to pass your shuttle run.
好的
Okay.
在此之前  我有个问题
But before we do this... question.
- 跑  - 好的
- Go! - Okay.
不要
No!
恶心
Gross!
快跑啊  乔伊  快跑
Run, Joey, run!
乔伊  你想和我一起去舞会吗
Joey, you want to go to prom?
不  不  不  不  不
No no no no no!
25.4 秒  你打破了校记录
25.4. That's a new school record.
我的儿子是个运动员
My son's a jock.
我的儿子居然是个运动员
My son's a jock!
好啊
Yeah.
多谢了  迪吉  这事没了你成不了
Thanks, Diggie. Couldn't have done it without you.
恭喜啦  亲爱的
Congratulations, little man.
谢谢了
Thanks.
我已经累得跑不动了
I'm too tired to run away.
我知道
I know.
好咧  各位都准备好干预一下玛蒂的行为了
Okay, so we are all here for Maddie's intervention.
我们一定要让她走进这间房间的时候
It is very important that we make her feel
感觉到这里是一个这是一个安全
like she's walking into a room that is safe,
充满着爱意和支持  小污点
and loving, and supportive and... Stains!
我真想把你手里的袋子拍掉
I am going to slap that bag out of your hands.
既然你不想任何人吃为啥还要把它们拿出来
Why did you put them out if you don't want anyone to eat them?
嘿
Hey...!
嘿啊
Hey.
嘿
你们在这干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
为什么都盯着我看
And why are you all staring at me?
为什么刚才维罗把前门锁了
And why did willow just lock the front door?
是啊  为什么呢
Yeah, why did she?
这让我有点儿紧张
It's making me nervous.
玛蒂  我们来这儿是为了谈谈你的问题的
Maddie, we are all here to talk to you about your problem.
什么问  我没有问题啊
What pro... I don't have a problem.
不  你有
Yeah, you do.
你对那些鞋子上瘾了
You're obsessed with those shoes.
我没有上瘾
I am not obsessed.
它们是我新的好朋友
They're just my new best friends
你的世界里唯一重要的东西
and the only things in the world that matter.
你以前告诉过我你多么讨厌高跟鞋
You used to tell me how you hated high heels.
我们周天的激励散步难道没有任何意义吗
Have our Sunday afternoon empowerment walk means nothing?!
呃
Okay.
我以前不喜欢高跟鞋  可是我现在喜欢了啊
So I used to not like them and now I do.
我说的是  一个女孩有权利改变主意
I mean, a girl has the right to change her mind
有权利改变主意了之后告诉她的朋友和家人
and also tell her friends and family
他们是多讨厌  别再烦一个可怜的女孩儿了
that they are annoying and should stop bothering her.
丽芙  是你告诉我去拥抱我的内在光芒的啊
I mean, Liv, you were the one who told me to embrace my inner sparkle.
是我说的没错  但是我发现我错了
I did, but I was wrong.
玛蒂  看看你  你现在的生活完全本末倒置了
I mean, Maddie, now your priorities are all out of whack.
你错过了一场比赛
You missed a game.
是啊  天  我都被逼上场了
Yeah, man. I had to play.
我进了个球  自摆乌龙
I made a basket... for the other team.
那我们说好去吃冰淇淋的事怎么办
And what about our fro-yo date?
玛蒂  那天冰淇淋还买一送一呢
Mads, it was two-for-one toppings night.
而且我讨厌你比我高
And I hate that you're taller than me.
这话真是出口为快
There. I said it.
我通过了往返跑哦
And I passed the shuttle run.
虽然和我们的对话并不相关  但我还是想说  我太自豪了
Not relevant to what we're talking about, but I'm just so proud of myself.
好了  伙计们  不过是一双  等等  你过了
Okay, guys, it's just a pair of... wait, hold on. You passed?
你知道吗  只要我想随时我都可以把它们脱下来
You know what? I can take these off whenever I want to.
哈
Ha!
好啊  那你脱啊
Okay, then do it.
恩  我说的是我想的时候
Well, I said that I can take them off whenever I want to,
但是我现在不想
and I just don't want to right now.
然后尼
So...
自己看着办吧
Deal with it.
噢  我们会的  大家动手啊
Oh, we will. Now!
迪吉  抓住她的腿
Diggie, grab her legs.
噢
Oh!
放我下来
Put me down!
这是怎  我的鞋子
Wha... my shoes!
丽芙  把我的鞋子还给我
Liv, give me back my shoes.
噢  松饼
Ooh! Muffins.
请别介意
Don't mind if I do.
丽芙  不要啊
Liv, no!
请别惩罚这双高跟鞋啊
Don't punish the pumps.
哦  相信我  玛蒂
Oh, believe me, Maddie.
这给我的伤害比给你的伤害多了去了
This is going to hurt me a lot more than it's going to hurt you.
哦  等等  我说啥来着
Oh... Wait, what am I saying?
难道丽芙·鲁尼能忍心
Like there's any way in the universe
可以毁掉一双超赞的……
that Liv Rooney would destroy the perfect pair of...
不
No!
这就结束了
It's over now.
一切都会好起来的
It's going to start to get better.
但是太难了
But this is so hard.
我的脚  要冻死了
And my feet are... So cold.
有些老朋友想打个招呼
I have a couple of old friends who want to say hi.
噢
Oh.
谢谢
Thank you.
哇
Wow.
我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
玛蒂  你找到了你的内在的光芒呀
Well, Maddie, you tapped into your inner sparkle.
是啊伙计  每个人都会这样
Yeah, man. It happens to all of us.
幸运的是  你有一个对这种闪闪发光的东西了如指掌的姐姐
Luckily, you have a sister to guide you through all things sparkly.
我们一步一步慢慢来
So we will start slow.
嗯  这是草莓味唇彩
Okay, this is strawberry lip gloss.
你可别把它吃了
Don't eat it.
给你  妈妈
Here you go, mom.
佛罗里达的橙子  刚刚榨的  杯子还是冰过的哦
Florida oranges, freshly squeezed, chilled glass.
我这就去烤面包
I'll go start on the croissants.
谢谢宝贝
Thank you, sweetie.
我不知道你是咋了  但是我喜欢
I don't know what's gotten into you, but I like it.
呃  我我这就要走了  鲁尼女士
Well, I'm on my way home, Mrs. Rooney.
埃文  这真是太感谢了
Evan... I cannot thank you enough.
我们两个的计划奏效了
Our plan worked perfectly.
谢谢你帮我重设帕克的行为逻辑
You did a brilliant job of helping me reprogram Parker.
鲁尼女士遇到问题了
Mrs. Rooney had a problem.
帕克在用他的方法逃避他该做的家务
Parker was using the Parker way to get out of all of his chores.
我告诉她  有一个不同的方法  更好的方法  埃文的方法
I told her, there's a different way, a better way, the Evan way.